<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The AIPhone Blog</title>
    <link>https://inubushi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The AIPhone Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 10:47:13 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://inubushi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Detection Vs. Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://inubushi.github.io/posts/detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 May 2020 10:47:13 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inubushi.github.io/posts/detection/</guid>
      <description>In the previous post, we learned what Image Classification is. To remind in simple terms, Image classification is the task of identifying the category of the dominant object in an image (photo, or camera preview). There is a list of categories that the classifier knows how to distinguish between, and the dominant object HAS TO belong to one of them, for meaningful results.
Image classification does have a variety of applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple iOS Coreml Demo: Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://inubushi.github.io/posts/simple-coreml-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 03:28:58 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inubushi.github.io/posts/simple-coreml-demo/</guid>
      <description>Image classification is a very basic task, in the point of view of humans. We just have to look at a photo that is supposed to belong to one of n categories, and tell which category it belongs to.
In AI terms, the photo is called an image; the categories are called classes. The AI (in our case a Deep Neural Network) processes the input image, and decides how likely it is to belong to each class.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Yubi&#39;s AIPhone Blog</title>
      <link>https://inubushi.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 13:48:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://inubushi.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>AI, particularly Deep Learning technology, is hot these days. With the easy-to-use CoreML framework and the fast Bionic neural processor, the iPhone is an excellent platform for AI apps. So, we should now be able to develop &amp;ldquo;AI apps&amp;rdquo; that provide great user experiences.
However, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to find good tutorials, repos and other resources that help us to develop AI apps for iPhone. AI tutorials focus mainly on the AI side, and iOS resources on this topic are hard to find.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>