<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-05-16T06:12:17+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000//</id><title type="html">Inubushi’s Projects</title><subtitle>I try to make gadgets and software that help people. When I think a project can be useful, I will share it here.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Mom’s Cards: a Custom Flashcard App</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/ios/apps,/autism/2017/05/02/mom-s-cards.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mom's Cards: a Custom Flashcard App" /><published>2017-05-02T06:30:00+09:00</published><updated>2017-05-02T06:30:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ios/apps,/autism/2017/05/02/mom-s-cards</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/ios/apps,/autism/2017/05/02/mom-s-cards.html">&lt;p&gt;Flashcards with sounds are a fun way for small children to learn words. However, most flashcard apps don’t allow you to create flashcards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is easier for kids to learn words if the flashcards show photos of things that they have seen around them; like their own stuff. And for some words (like “grandma”), you have to make your own cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My Karuta is an easy-to-use flashcard app. You can make your own flashcards, with photos and sounds. Make flashcards with things the child sees around him, to make learning words easy and fast. Hearing the voice of mom, dad, or even a loving grandpa, will add both fun and motivation!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use your imaginations to make more interesting content; you can record storybooks, teach letters, and do many more things with this single app!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We made My Karuta to help a child who had trouble learning words, and found it very helpful. We now share it with you for free, and hope it will help many more kids!&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Flashcards with sounds are a fun way for small children to learn words. However, most flashcard apps don’t allow you to create flashcards.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mom’s Timer: a Timer App for Autistic Kids</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/ios/apps,/autism/2017/05/02/mom-s-timer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mom's Timer: a Timer App for Autistic Kids" /><published>2017-05-02T06:30:00+09:00</published><updated>2017-05-02T06:30:00+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ios/apps,/autism/2017/05/02/mom-s-timer</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/ios/apps,/autism/2017/05/02/mom-s-timer.html">&lt;p&gt;I founded &lt;a href=&quot;http://yubi.ml&quot;&gt;Yubi&lt;/a&gt;, a small business that designs snd develops mobile apps, in 2009. At Yubi, I help both indie and medium scall app developers to improve the user experiences of their apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yubi creates its own apps, too. Today, we launched “&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/moms-timer/id1230221153?ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;Mom’s Timer&lt;/a&gt;”, a timer app for autistic children.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kids with autism find it troublesome to keep track of time and end up taking a lot of time even for simple tasks. If you are a parent of an autistic kid, you know how much time is wasted while waiting for him to finish what he/she is doing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mom’s Timer is designed to help motivate autistic kids to finish what they are doing. Simply set the duration, and also a photo of any reward that the child will get if he finishes in time. The timer will start hiding the photo gradually, giving the child an idea of the remaining time and the consequences of dilly-dallying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We made Mom’s Timer to help a child who had trouble learning words, and found it very helpful. We now share it with you for free, and hope it will help many more kids!&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">I founded Yubi, a small business that designs snd develops mobile apps, in 2009. At Yubi, I help both indie and medium scall app developers to improve the user experiences of their apps.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Using Eigen on iOS</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/ios/programming/2017/04/20/using-eigen-with-ios.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Using Eigen on iOS" /><published>2017-04-20T06:27:27+09:00</published><updated>2017-04-20T06:27:27+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/ios/programming/2017/04/20/using-eigen-with-ios</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/ios/programming/2017/04/20/using-eigen-with-ios.html">&lt;p&gt;Eigen is a collection of platform independent libraries for mathematical computations. It is popular because of being open-source, too. Developing OS X apps that use Eigen is straightforward. Just include the correct headers, and you are done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, things are not that easy when it comes to iOS apps. Several compiler errors have been reported.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The good news is, doing two things can fix most of these problems:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;put #include directives relating to Eigen at the top of the program file.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;under the Build Settings of the project, look for “C++ Language Dialect” and “C++ Standard Library” settings. Instead of “Compiler Default”, you can selecting different settings. I do not want to suggest a particular setting because that might clash with other libraries that you have included.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><summary type="html">Eigen is a collection of platform independent libraries for mathematical computations. It is popular because of being open-source, too. Developing OS X apps that use Eigen is straightforward. Just include the correct headers, and you are done.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Activity Recognition with Deep Neural Networks</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/deep/learning/2017/04/20/activity-recognition-with-deep-learning.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Activity Recognition with Deep Neural Networks" /><published>2017-04-20T06:27:27+09:00</published><updated>2017-04-20T06:27:27+09:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/deep/learning/2017/04/20/activity-recognition-with-deep-learning</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/deep/learning/2017/04/20/activity-recognition-with-deep-learning.html">&lt;p&gt;Automatically recognizing people’s activity by analyzing videos can save a lot of time when there is a need to go through a lare amount of surveillance camera video. Some researchers have tried this using deep learning approaches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While there are a few good research papers on how to use deep learning for human activity recognition in video, I am yet to see a good demo that can get a beginner started. So, I thought of creating one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out my repository &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/inubushi/LSTM-KTH&quot;&gt;LSTM-KTH&lt;/a&gt; for an example of using convolutional neural networks and LSTM recurrent neural networks for recognizing activity in the KTH dataset.&lt;/p&gt;</content><summary type="html">Automatically recognizing people’s activity by analyzing videos can save a lot of time when there is a need to go through a lare amount of surveillance camera video. Some researchers have tried this using deep learning approaches.</summary></entry></feed>
